<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Vanilla Factions Expanded - Medieval 2</name>
	<author>Oskar Potocki, xrushha, Taranchuk, Sarg Bjornson, Oracle of Thessia</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.5</li>
		<li>1.6</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>OskarPotocki.VFE.Medieval2</packageId>
	<description>A worthy successor to our beloved Vanilla Factions Expanded - Medieval and Vanilla Factions Expanded - Vikings, VFE-Medieval 2 builds upon everything that made the originals great. While this isn’t a medieval overhaul that removes late game content in favor of medieval content, we’ve carefully designed it to seamlessly fill the gap between the neolithic and industrial eras, ensuring medieval technologies remain relevant even as you advance.

Here’s what you can look forward to:

- New Medieval Factions &amp; Warfare: Encounter fortified castles, viking towns and merchants’ caravans. Engage in castle sieges and skirmishes, as well as barter!
- Meaningful Medieval Technology: Unlock medieval advancements that don’t become obsolete: matchlock firearms, alchemy, and powerful fortifications that remain useful well into the industrial era.
- New Economy &amp; Industry: Produce fine wines, rich honey, and crafted armors, establishing a thriving medieval economy that supports both trade and warfare.
- Expanded Crafting &amp; Equipment: Wield an expanded arsenal of medieval weaponry, from warbows and arbalests to halberds and pikes with extended attack range, and dress your warriors and base in custom heraldic apparel and structures, displaying your faction's colors.
- Challenging Storyteller: Maynard Medieval: A storyteller who embraces drama, suffering, and slow technological progress, forcing you to earn every breakthrough through blood and toil.

After many months of development, Medieval 2 is our most refined medieval era expansion yet, delivering a unique experience without restricting your playstyle or halting your technological progression.
</description>
	<modIconPath IgnoreIfNoMatchingField="True">UI/VELogo</modIconPath>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</packageId>
			<displayName>Vanilla Expanded Framework</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2023507013</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		
		<li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</li>
	</loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>